https://www.baggallini.com/privacy-policy.html

skip to content
Please read our accessibility statement.
free shipping on orders $100+
search catalog
search by keyword, style, etc.
close menu
Your shopping bag is empty.
Promo Code
have a promo code?
privacy policy
baggallini.com. is owned by the R.G. Barry Corporation. For a list of all of R.G. Barry Corporation brands, please visit www.rgbarry.com.
Thank you for visiting the baggallini.com website. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of the baggallini.com website or our services, the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and choices about such uses and disclosures. By visiting the baggallini.com website, you are confirming your agreement to our privacy policies as described in this Privacy Policy. You should also review our Terms of Use for more information about the policies governing your use of the baggallini.com website.
Visiting the baggallini.com website from outside the United States
This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on the baggallini.com website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting the baggallini.com website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.
Security
baggallini.com has imposed confidentiality obligations on its service providers who will have access to the personal information collected on this site. In addition, we have implemented administrative, technical and physical measures to address the confidentiality of personal information collected on this website. We use secure-socket-layer (SSL) certificate authentication to protect order information during transmission by encrypting all sensitive information transmitted during your shopping experience. SSL is encryption technology that provides security for information that's transmitted over the Internet. This site accepts orders only from web browsers that permit communication through SSL technology. We also reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order.
While we implement the above security measures for this website, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible.
information we collect
Personal Information
We may collect and store personally identifiable information on certain areas of the baggallini.com website when users register, purchase products or services, request information or a response, sign up for sweepstakes or contests, or participate in user posting areas, such as bulletin boards, discussion forums, reviews and surveys, and social media platforms.
Such personally identifiable information may include but is not limited to your name, address, age, date of birth, sex, e-mail address, telephone numbers, information about your interests and activities and your reviews of our website or products that we sell. We may combine the personally identifiable information that we receive from you through the baggallini.com website with information from other sources included but not limited to social media platforms.
If you transact business with us, such personally identifiable information may also include financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). You may elect not to provide certain types of information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of the baggallini.com website.
We may also collect and store personally identifiable information about other people that you provide to us. If you use the baggallini.com website to send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) a product as a gift, information that may interest them or messages (such as invitations) through our system, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of each such recipient.
Other Information
We may also automatically collect and store certain types of anonymous information about your shopping experiences when you visit the baggallini.com website by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. “Cookies” are small files placed on the hard drive of your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit our web site, what pages you view, where you go after you leave the site and what you may have placed in your shopping bag. The cookies track your computer, not you. They are used to facilitate access to the baggallini.com website and to personalize your on-line experience.
We may also use internet technology like Web beacons on our site and in e-mail messages to determine whether pages and messages have been opened and acted upon. A “web beacon” is an electronic image placed in the code of a web page. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize and improve the services we offer visitors to the baggallini.com website to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our on-line advertising and content or other activities.
We may in the future allow third-party advertising companies to use cookies when you visit baggallini.com. These selected companies may use information (not including your name, address, credit card information, email address, or telephone number) about your choice to visit our website and your visits to other websites to provide advertisements about our products on this and other websites. These selected companies also provide this information to us which we use to gauge the effectiveness of the advertisements they place about our products and for marketing purposes. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about no longer having information from these third-party cookies used by these companies or provided to us, click here.
Children's Privacy Protection
The baggallini.com website is not intentionally designed for or directed at children under 13 years of age and we will not intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13.
use and sharing of information
Personal and Other information that we collect from customers and users of the baggallini.com website is used to improve our relevance to you and to improve your shopping experience with us. We use the information that you provide so that we may provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to fulfill your requests for information, and to manage our business. In addition, we may send you by e-mail or offline offerings of products or services that we think may be of interest to you or ask you to participate in activities such as special surveys. We may also use personally identifiable information collected at baggallini.com combined with the other information in analyzing the behavior of users of the baggallini.com website in order to measure interest in specific items posted on the website.
baggallini.com may share personal information with other brands within R.G. Barry Corporation’s family of brands. It is possible that this policy will change in the future. If we do decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice in this Privacy Policy and on our home page.
We may use other information -- i.e. non-personally identifiable information, summary or aggregate information that we collect to improve the design and content of the baggallini.com website, or content from social media platforms -- to enable us to further enhance your experience with the baggallini brand and for other business purposes. We may also share such aggregate information with third parties.
baggallini.com may share your personal information with companies that perform services for us, such as fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mails, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, investigating fraudulent activity, conducting customer surveys, and providing customer service
We may also share your personally identifiable information that you provide to us as may be required by law or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law or is necessary to protect the users of our website, the site or the public or to enforce our Terms of Use.
Personally identifiable information that you have provided to us on baggallini.com is an asset of R.G. Barry Corporation that may be included in assets transferred to an acquirer if R.G. Barry Corporation is acquired by a third party or the baggallini brand is sold to a third party or it sells or transfers a particular portion of its business assets.
Reviews and other Posted Information
We may provide areas on the baggallini.com website where you can post information including reviews of products. Such postings are governed by our Terms of Use. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on publicly-viewable Web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your e-mail address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. Once you have posted information, you will not be able to edit or delete such information.
Your Choices Regarding Personal Information
You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may result in you being unable to use certain features of the baggallini.com website because such information may be required in order for you to register as a member, purchase products or services, participate in a contest, promotion, survey, or sweepstakes, ask a question, or initiate other transactions on the baggallini.com website.
Unsubscribe from baggallini.com Mailing List
At any time, you may choose to no longer receive e-mails from baggallini.com:
By contacting us at privacy@baggallini.com
Unsubscribing from our email list via the unsubscribe link in a baggallini.com marketing email
It may take up to 10 days for us to process an opt-out request. We may send you other types of transactional and relationship e-mail communications, such as service announcements, administrative notices, and surveys, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.
Correction of Personal Information
If you create an Account, you may revise the information you have provided for your Account by following the instructions on the My Account page of the baggallini.com website.
California Privacy Rights
Under California law, if you are a resident of California, you have the right to control how your personal information is shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Following receipt of a request from you, we will provide you with a cost-free means of informing us that you do not want your personal information to be shared with third parties for the direct marketing purposes of such third parties. If you would like to exercise your right under California law to tell us that you do not wish your personal information to be shared with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, you should send your written request to privacy@baggallini.com or the mailing address at the end of this page. We will respond to your request within 30 days.
Links
For your convenience and enjoyment, baggallini.com and its other marketing channels may contain links to other websites. We do not evaluate and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, and we urge you to review the privacy policies on each link to ensure that you are comfortable with their privacy policies and practices.
Contact our Privacy Department
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information handling practices, please contact us at privacy@baggallini.com, or
R.G. Barry Corporation baggallini Privacy Officer 13405 Yarmouth Road NW Pickerington, OH 43147
This Privacy Policy was last updated on: October 9, 2015.
Be the first to know about exclusive deals, early product access, and more! We'll sweeten the deal with 20% off your first full price purchase*
Thank you for signing up!
sign up
Sign up to receive a 20% off promo code in your inbox. *Offer valid on full-price items. Must be a new email subscriber. Additional terms may apply.
